https://www.informedparent.co.uk/tip-privacy-policy/

Shouldn't the after-effects of vaccination be discussed before?
TIP Privacy Policy
This Policy is effective as of May 25th, 2018 and compliant with GDPR.
What is GDPR?
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) was passed by the EU Parliament in April of 2016. Replacing the Data Protection Directive from the 90s, it’s the biggest overarching legislative change in data privacy regulation to take place the last 20 years.
GDPR was created to standardize data privacy laws throughout Europe—and to put greater protection on the data privacy of EU citizens. The big changes are:
A Change in Legislative Scope: Now, all controllers and processors in the EU are subject to GDPR—even if the data they’re accessing is processed outside of the EU. The reverse is also true. If you’re a company processing the data of EU citizens (either to offer goods and services, or to monitor behavior taking place in the EU)—it doesn’t matter where you’re based, or where you’re processing the data. You still have to comply with GDPR.
Greater Penalties for noncompliance: The maximum fine for noncompliance with GDPR is up to 4% of annual global turnover, or 20 million euros—depending on which is greater.
Strengthened Conditions for Consent: No more legalese. Consent has to be given in an easy, accessible way before processing a persons data. You also have to disclose the purpose for that data processing, and make it as easy to withdraw consent as to give it.
A full list of the key GDPR changes can be found on the EU GDPR website here.
TIP Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how The Informed Parent Co.Ltd. uses and protects any information that you give The Informed Parent Co. Ltd. when you use this website.
The Informed Parent Co.Ltd. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
The Informed Parent Co.Ltd. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at: tip.admin1@informedparent.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to: The Informed Parent, PO Box 4481, Worthing, West Sussex, BN11 2WH.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
TweetPinShare0 Shares
Follow TIP on Twitter!The Informed ParentFollowThe Informed Parent@informedparent_·17hShould we trust a vaccine produced by Convicted Felons? https://covidwatching.org/can-we-trust-a-vaccine-produced-by-convicted-felons/Reply on Twitter 1336990323944415232Retweet on Twitter 13369903239444152321Like on Twitter 13369903239444152324Twitter 1336990323944415232The Informed Parent@informedparent_·8 Dechttps://www.ukmedfreedom.org/aboutReply on Twitter 1336373495564001280Retweet on Twitter 1336373495564001280Like on Twitter 13363734955640012801Twitter 1336373495564001280Retweet on TwitterThe Informed Parent RetweetedRobin Monotti@robinmonotti·25 NovITALY: CONFIRMED BY ITALIAN HEALTH SERVICE: False positives to Covid19 test as diagnosis are 95%. Legal cases started against testing under charges of fraud to procure public funding, false alarm, ideological false, and manslaughter. Reply on Twitter 1331500903564775426Retweet on Twitter 13315009035647754267311Like on Twitter 133150090356477542610976Twitter 1331500903564775426Retweet on TwitterThe Informed Parent RetweetedYardley Yeadon@MichaelYeadon3·19 NovPortuguese Court Rules PCR Tests As Unreliable & Unlawful To Quarantine People
https://greatgameindia.com/portuguese-court-pcr-tests-unreliable/Reply on Twitter 1329225324383662080Retweet on Twitter 13292253243836620802987Like on Twitter 13292253243836620806258Twitter 1329225324383662080The Informed Parent@informedparent_·15 Novhttps://youtu.be/mcm8Sc8f66oReply on Twitter 1327992153579139094Retweet on Twitter 13279921535791390941Like on Twitter 13279921535791390942Twitter 1327992153579139094Load More...
This site uses cookies:
Find out more HERE, or clickACCEPT
